<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/xsl/atom.xsl" media="all"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <id>https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/</id>
  <title>Kaleem Clarkson</title>
  <subtitle><![CDATA[A Keynote Speaker who is passionate about work-life integration and location-independence.]]></subtitle>
  <link href="https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2025-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Kaleem Clarkson</name>
    <uri>https://www.kaleemclarkson.com</uri>
  </author>
  <entry xml:lang="en">
    <id>https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/about/</id>
    <title>About Kaleem</title>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1 id="about-kaleem">About Kaleem</h1>
<p>Kaleem is a husband, father, remote work advocate, people operations professional, and speaker. He is the Chief Operating Officer of <a href="https://bit.ly/2Swje5w" rel="noopener noreferrer">Blend Me, Inc</a> a fractional people operations consultancy that helps startups and small businesses transform into high-functioning remote or hybrid-remote workplaces.
 
With nearly 20 years of strategic operations and event planning experience, he helps leadership implement<a href="https://www.blendmeinc.com/remote-people-operations" rel="noopener noreferrer"> people operations solutions</a> that increase productivity and engagement for both internal and external stakeholders. He is passionate about<a href="https://www.blendmeinc.com/article/work-life-balance-vs-work-life-integration" rel="noopener noreferrer"> work-life integration</a> and maximizing <a href="https://www.blendmeinc.com/the-remote-employee-experience" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Remote Employee Experience (TREE). </a></p>
<p>Kaleem was born and raised in Bangor, Maine, the home of Stephen King. He is a graduate of Worcester State University. He has been featured in<a href="https://hbr.org/2020/11/how-to-find-out-if-a-companys-culture-is-right-for-you" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Harvard Business Review</a>, CNBC, Fortune Magazine, named to LinkedIn’s <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/linkedin-top-voices-remote-work-10-creators-follow-linkedin-news-1c/" rel="noopener noreferrer">Top 10 Voices in Remote Work</a>, and listed as one of the<a href="https://www.allamericanspeakers.com/blog/remote-work-advocates/" rel="noopener noreferrer"> top 15 Remote Work Advocates</a> by the All-American Speakers Bureau. Kaleem has presented alongside leadership from companies such as Google, United Airlines, Facebook, Visa, and HP.</p>
<p>Kaleem currently resides in Atlanta, Georgia with his family. When he is not working, you can find him mountain biking on the trails of Georgia with his headphones, blasting a little hard rock music.</p>]]>
    </content>
    <link href="https://www.kaleemclarkson.com/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
    <published>2025-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2025-11-10T20:40:00+00:00</updated>
  </entry>
</feed>
